{
    "title": "FINAL DRAFT",
    "range": "Lesson1〜3",
    "quizzes": [
        {
            "question": "今朝、インターネットにアクセスできなかった。",
            "answer": "解答1"
        },
        {
            "question": "ネットサーフィンをした。",
            "answer": "解答2"
        },
        {
            "question": "インターネットを（いろいろと）見た。",
            "answer": "解答3"
        },
        {
            "question": "その写真がバズった。",
            "answer": "解答4"
        },
        {
            "question": "インターネットで情報を探してみます。",
            "answer": "解答5"
        },
        {
            "question": "去年、うちの学校はオンラインで授業を行った。",
            "answer": "解答6"
        },
        {
            "question": "私はインターネットの発達に関する記事を読んだ。",
            "answer": "解答7"
        },
        {
            "question": "私たちは正確な情報だけが欲しいです。",
            "answer": "解答8"
        },
        {
            "question": "最新の情報については当社のウェブサイトをご覧ください。",
            "answer": "解答9"
        },
        {
            "question": "これは正確で信頼できる情報ですか？",
            "answer": "解答10"
        },
        {
            "question": "こういったアプリによって、私の生活は便利になった。",
            "answer": "These apps have made my life easier."
        },
        {
            "question": "インターネットの発達により、私たちは以前よりも多くの情報を手に入れられるようになった。",
            "answer": "The development of the Internet has enabled us to get more information than before."
        },
        {
            "question": "インターネットの発達により、私たちの生活は驚くほど便利になった。",
            "answer": "The development of the Internet has made our daily lives much easier."
        },
        {
            "question": "私の姉のツイートはバズった。",
            "answer": "My sister’s tweet went viral."
        },
        {
            "question": "私はレポートを書くとき、普段はインターネットで情報を得ている。",
            "answer": "I usually get information on the Internet when I write a paper."
        },
        {
            "question": "私は靴を1足ネット通販で買った。",
            "answer": "I bought a pair of shoes online."
        },

        {
            "question": "彼はインターネットを1時間（いろいろと）見た。",
            "answer": "He browsed the Internet for an hour."
        },
        {
            "question": "インターネットの発達によって、世界は大きく変わった。",
            "answer": "The development of the Internet has completely changed the world."
        },
        {
            "question": "このソフトウェアによって、私の仕事ははるかに簡単になった。",
            "answer": "This software has made my job much easier."
        },
        {
            "question": "インターネットのおかげで、私たちは一瞬で最新情報を手に入れられるようになった。",
            "answer": "The Internet has made it possibe for us to quickly get the latest information."
        },
        {
            "question": "人々は、書きたいものをなんでもネットに書き込む。",
            "answer": "People write whatever they want on the Internet."
        },
        {
            "question": "服をネット通販で買う人が急速に増えてきた。",
            "answer": "The number of people who buy clothes online has increased rapidly."
        },
        {
            "question": "コンピューターやスマホがどれだけ普及しているかを考えれば、オンラインで勉強している人が増えているのも当然だろう。",
            "answer": "If you consider haw common computers and smartphones have become, it is natural that the number of people who study online is increasing."
        }
    ]
}